<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-05T01:27:51-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to My Blog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to My Blog" /><published>2020-01-04T23:51:58-05:00</published><updated>2020-01-04T23:51:58-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/04/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2020/01/04/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I’m Cody Seibert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone unaware, I’m growing a &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com/c/codyseibert&quot;&gt;YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; where I post a lot of videos related to coding tutorials, talks about software, and mini projects. The main focus of the channel is web development, but I also play around with artificial intelligence, such as in this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zh8smVUwrns&amp;amp;t=5s&quot;&gt;video where I build an AI to jump over blocks&lt;/a&gt;, and computer vision, such as in &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;this video where I teach about template matching&lt;/a&gt;, and sometimes game programming like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5tbepogkt3c&quot;&gt;this time lapse video of me building PONG using Javascript&lt;/a&gt;. The plan for this blog is to help me get organized and collect my thoughts of these various tutorials and put them in writing so that a larger audience can still learn about the topics I speak about without having to invest time in watching a full video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So who am I and why do I think I’m qualified to post videos about software? I’m a full stack engineer who has been working in the industry going on 5 years now. Back in 2013 I graduated from the University of Central Florida with a Bachelor’s degree of Computer Science. At college, I was part of the programming team for a year where we were taught how to solve complex program problems working as a team of 3 students. Prior to college, I took a couple of programming classes in high school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still have a ton to learn about software engineering, but I’d like to start sharing the things I have learned over the years with the community of programmers. My goals for this blog is to at least post 1 blog post a day, and I think I can achieve it if I put my mind to it. Writing isn’t my strongest skill, so I think a post a day will help my abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hey everyone! I’m Cody Seibert.</summary></entry></feed>